Bull Shark is a horror, thriller film directed by Brett Bentman.
A hungry shark begins feeding on some unsuspecting
lake goers in a small Texas town.
Spencer Timms, played by Thom Hallum.
Nolan Holt, played by Billy Blair.
Dottie Timms, played by Lindsey Marie Wilson.
Sherrif Wilson, played by Derrick Redford.
Reema, played by Colleen Elizabeth Miller.
Grant Timms, played by Colin Heintz.
The bull shark (Carcharhinus leucas), also known as the Zambezi shark (informally zambi) in Africa and Lake Nicaragua shark in
Nicaragua, is a species of requiem shark commonly found worldwide in warm, shallow waters along coasts and in rivers.
It is known for its aggressive nature, and presence mainly in warm, shallow brackish and
freshwater systems including estuaries and (usually) lower reaches of rivers.
Their aggressive nature has led to ongoing shark-culling efforts near beaches to protect
beachgoers, which is one of the causes of bull shark populations continuing to decrease.
Bull sharks are listed as vulnerable on the IUCN Red List.
Bull sharks are euryhaline and can thrive in both salt and fresh water.
They are known to travel far up rivers, and have been known to travel up the Mississippi River as far as Alton, Illinois,
about 1,100 kilometres (700 mi) from the ocean, but few freshwater interactions with humans have been recorded.
Larger-sized bull sharks are probably responsible for the majority of nearshore shark
attacks, including many incidents of shark bites attributed to other species.
Unlike the river sharks of the genus Glyphis, bull sharks are not true freshwater
sharks, despite their ability to survive in freshwater habitats.
This shark appears in the image of the 2000 colones banknote from Costa Rica.
The film explores themes of shark attack, shark, grand, bullshark.
The tone is dark and intense.